<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICUP</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="featuredcontent">Featured Content</string>
    <string name="emptylist">Nothing to display</string>
    <string name="eventdir">Event Directory</string>
    <string name="eventlist">Loading Events...</string>
    <string name="organizationdir">Loading Organizations...</string>
    <string name="organizationcat">Organization Category</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="userName">User Name:</string>
    <string name="password">Password:</string>
    <string name="ZipCode">Zip Code:</string>
    <string name="Radius">Radius:</string>
    <string name="Advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="eventcat">Events Category</string>
	<string name="createAccountText"><u>Create Account</u></string>
	<string name="icupWelcomeText">Welcome to lokalite mobile! Here you\'ll find a 
				tutorial on the application as well as the background on the company.</string>
	<string name="icupInfoText">\nlokalite is a small, Boulder-based, startup company specializing
	in the distribution of information and advertisements. lokalite plans to showcase events and 
	organization profiles of local businesses within the community. For the time being, the company
	plans on targeting the Boulder community for its clients. The events and organizations advertised 
	through lokalite will be from Boulder. lokalite will expand to cover events and organizations 
	to other cities and states.\n\n
	Through lokalite mobile! users are able to access an Events List, Organizations List, and a 
	Featured Content from the lokalite server. The Events List and Organizations List is
	organized into categories and allows for users to search through by various criterion: location, 
	date, and time. The Featured Content displays either a featured Event or Organization and is 
	updated on a daily basis. lokalite mobile! also features a Favorites List, allowing users to add 
	and remove Events, Organizations, and Featured content to and from it. Users will be able to map 
	all Events, Organizations, and Featured Content with Google Maps. Users will also be able to set
	notifications (i.e. vibrate or play a sound) which will alert the user of an upcoming Event.\n </string>
	
	<string name="linktolokalite"> Check out <a href="http://www.lokalite.com"> lokalite\'s website</a> for more details and features! </string>

</resources>
